Previously on Heated Rivalry...
Why the fuck
did you think it was OK
to sext me before the game?
You were hard, weren't you?
Wow! This Montreal girl
works you up, brother.
You're straight up blushing.
Never have I blushed.
Russians do not do this.
Obviously, we won't
see each other
during the Games, right?
Russia has been eliminated
from medal contention.
A hard pill to swallow
for Ilya Rozanov.
How are you not ashamed?
I'm ashamed, Father.
You didn't answer my text.
Go away, Hollander.
We are not anything.
What the fuck
do you want, Rozanov?
You won't even
acknowledge I exist,
so, yeah, what the fuck
do you actually want from me?
I need...
Tell me.
I need you.
Marleau cutting through center.
Drops it back for Rozanov,
who's all alone.
Rozanov dekes, he scores!
Hollander on the ice for both
of Rozanov's goals tonight.
Having a good night?
That's nice. I think there's
still time for a hat trick.
Should I do now
or wait till last second?
'Cause I don't know.
Last second is more fun, but...
Rozanov scores!
Hollander is really gonna
want that last one back.
The Montreal captain wants
this whole night back.
♪♪ My moon, my man,
so changeable ♪
♪ And such a
loveable lamb to me ♪
♪ My care, my coat
leave on a high note ♪
♪ There's nowhere to go but on ♪
♪ Heart on my sleeve,
not where it should be ♪
♪ The song's out of key again ♪
♪ My moon's white face,
what day and what phase ♪
♪ It's the calendar page again ♪
♪ Take it slow,
take it easy on me ♪
♪ And shed some light,
shed some light on me please ♪
And show me that label!
All right! And that's where
we freeze camera!
And that's our commercial!
All right, guys.
Let's reset this.
New cans. New cans.
Shut your eyes.
♪ My moon and me,
not as good as we've been ♪
♪ It's the dirtiest clean
I know ♪
♪ My care, my coat
leave on a high note ♪
♪ There's nowhere to go ♪
Yeah, yeah!
♪ Shed some light on me please ♪
♪ Take it slow,
take it easy on me ♪
♪ And shed some light ♪
♪ Shed some light on me please ♪
For the first time in 16 years,
the Montreal Metros
are hoisting the MLH Cup.
What a feeling it must be
for captain Shane Hollander!
♪ My moon ♪
♪ The moon and my man ♪
-All right, Shane, you good?
-Ready to go?
-Am I walking...
-Do the same thing.
That's great, Shane.
Look over your shoulder.
You look great!
Take a look at the camera.
Directly into the camera.
Hit that mark and give me
that pose. That's it.
♪ There's nowhere to go but up ♪
♪ Heart on my sleeve ♪
♪ Not where it should be ♪
♪ The song's out of key again ♪
♪ Take it slow,
take it easy on me ♪
♪ And shed some light,
shed some light on me please ♪
♪ Take it slow,
take it easy on me ♪
-Ah, no!
-It should have been me!
Blah!
Can we call it a dynasty?
Shane Hollander
and the Montreal Metros
are your MLH champions
for the second year in a row.
Not since Chicago
in the late '90s
have we seen a team
take home back-to-back cups.
♪ My care, my coat ♪
♪ There's nowhere to go ♪
♪ Take it slow ♪
♪ Take it easy on me ♪
♪ And shed some light,
shed some light on me please ♪
♪ Take it slow,
take it easy on me ♪
♪ And shed some light,
shed some light on me please ♪
Well, I like him,
but he was the kid
Mom was bullying
because he was the worst player.
He had no hand-eye coord...
♪ My moon ♪
♪ The moon and my man ♪
-Purple.
-Right!
What color is a cucumber?
Sorry, Shane, can we...
Yeah, sorry, we're just...
We're gonna roll now.
OK, that's right.
OK, wow, that's the stuff!
That's the money, my friend.
♪ My moon ♪
♪ The moon and my man ♪♪
-She's what?
-Pregnant.
Jacki's pregnant.
Again?
Jesus Christ, man.
You gotta work on your lying.
"Hayden, what great news!"
"Hayden, I'm so happy for you!"
No, I mean, a fourth kid,
that's awesome, man. Really.
Holy shit, dude.
You can't find me!
Ruby! Emma! Slow down!
I mean,
she's fucking bored, right?
Fair enough.
-Come here!
-Ruby...
Ruby!
How do you know it's Ruby?
'Cause she's a beast.
So?
So what?
So when are you gonna
join me in this nightmare?
You want to get me pregnant too?
I don't think I'm ready.
I think I still have some
good hockey left in me.
You're an asshole. You ever
talk to that ex of yours?
What was it, Jennifer?
-Uh, Jessica.
-Jessica!
You ever hit that?
Don't say "hit that."
Sorry, Virgin Mary.
I'm not...
Here, tag! You are it.
Let's go see Uncle Shane!
Oh, yeah!
Look, I'm just saying, man,
if you ever do, you could
bring her around, you know?
We'd do couple stuff.
It'd be fun.
-I'm not...
-I mean, she's...
I don't see her anymore.
I think she's
engaged or something.
Fair enough. So, um...
Jacki has this friend, right?
-Hayd...
-What?
Dude, she's fucking hot.
She teaches, like,
mommy yoga or something.
Maybe it's just stretching,
but she's fucking hot.
And she's funny.
Swear jar, two times.
-Oh, fuck.
-Three.
OK, come on, man. Why not?
Can I just show you her Insta?
-Fine.
-Yes! OK, good.
Jacki will be happy.
We both have to make
your wife happy now?
Yeah, damn right we do.
If you want her to
make your gross food
and keep my house stocked
with ginger ale.
-Stop it!
-Oh, Jesus Christ.
Ruby, you're gonna kill her.
Tell your dad to leave me alone.
Um, excuse me?
Are you Shane Hollander?
Yeah.
Oh my God!
Can we get a picture with you?
Um, I kind of have
my hands full at the moment.
Um, could you hold
his baby for him, please,
so we can get a picture?
"Hold his baby"?
I'm sorry, buddy!
Hey, first of all,
it's my fucking baby.
Four times.
-And second...
-Wait, do I have all the kids?
Oh, you're the worst one!
You can't say
stuff like that to her.
It's true. Second, they didn't
even fucking recognize me.
-Ding, ding, ding!
-We've hit five times.
That's when I'm
supposed to text Jacki.
-I'm telling on you, Daddy!
-Narc!
Narc, narc!
I'm getting a vasectomy.
Way too late.
But this is
Shane Hollander's
fortress of solitude.
Here in Eastern Quebec
is the house he had built
on a private lake.
It's my favorite place on Earth.
My parents' cottage,
where I spent summers,
is 10 minutes away.
I'm ready.
Unless you've decided
we should stay in and watch...
whatever this is.
Sorry.
It's so fucking boring
I almost fell into a coma.
Mmm.
He's fucking hot, though.
Are you seeing
anyone these days?
Are you jealous?
No. I think you know me
better than that.
So there's no one serious?
Nope.
Not even Jane?
What?
You've been texting for years.
I thought maybe it was serious.
Or something.
It's not serious.
Or anything.
OK.
Sasha says hi.
I'm, uh, heading out for a bit.
Cool.
Uh, to meet a friend.
Nice!
I'll be back later.
I won't wait up.
It's not like that.
It's just a... a friend.
So Lily's just a buddy?
What?
Chill. I know you text a Lily.
I don't.
OK, go get laid, weirdo.
Or don't. I don't care.
I hope you do.
You play better after.
Go fuck yourself.
-Oh, I plan to.
-Probably more than once.
Love a hotel room.
-Gross.
-Bye!
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Do I take my shoes off?
No, you're good.
Wow.
Wow!
This place is great.
Did you get this built,
or do you know who did?
Mr. Real Estate.
That's not what
I meant. I just...
You think we need to talk?
No, after.
OK.
Oh!
I should go.
Or you could stay.
Stay?
Here tonight.
I'm not done with you.
And we have
afternoon game tomorrow,
so no morning practice.
I told Hayden.
Is Hayden your mother?
No.
No, he's not?
Fuck off.
Who cares what you told Hayden?
Stay.
OK.
OK?
Mmm.
I'm hungry.
For what?
For food, pervert.
Hey.
You like tuna melt?
You want to make me a tuna melt?
-I was gonna make one for me.
-I can make two.
You head to Florida
after this, right?
Yeah, right after the game.
Tampa, then Sunrise,
then we go to Dallas
and St. Louis.
Ah, all the hot spots.
Ginger ale cold enough?
Yeah, it's great.
Good.
Food will be ready soon.
Jesus Christ!
You know this guy, Ryan Price?
Yeah, from playing against him
and not wanting to fight him.
You did a season
with him, right?
Mmm. He is not
what you would think.
How so?
Like, he's quiet.
Doesn't talk.
Keeps to himself.
Not bad guy.
Doesn't make friends.
Well, he gets traded
every season.
Tough to make friends that way.
Probably he wants
to get traded again.
Buffalo is terrible.
Yeah, and their team sucks too.
And people say you're not funny.
They do?
Yeah. They say
you're boring, too.
Who says that?
Me.
What's your, uh,
favorite city to play in?
-On the road?
-Mmm...
I like New York,
'cause it's New York.
They fucking hate me there.
They hate you everywhere.
No, not Florida.
It's full of Boston people.
And you?
Uh, I like Ottawa,
'cause it's my hometown.
Toronto, Winnipeg...
I'm happy they have
a team again.
What, are those boring answers?
Yes.
Well, I like the hot places too.
Mmm.
Hot, like weather hot.
Ah, OK.
LA is hot.
Hot women.
Yeah, sure. I mean,
there are hot women everywhere.
There is a girl I like here
very much, Svetlana.
Oh?
She's old friend, from Russia.
Her father was famous goaltender
of Soviet team.
She knows everything
about hockey.
Cool.
And she likes you very much.
Oh.
That's nice.
So she's, like, your girlfriend?
No, no. Nothing like that.
She's old friend.
Sometimes we fuck, but...
she's busy these days, you know,
new business selling fancy cars.
Sounds perfect for you.
Yes, it's close to that, but...
But what?
But it's nothing more
than that for either of us.
But it's nice to have
regular woman like that around.
You think she's the only woman
in Boston who'd sleep with you?
Mmm.
I think I will
find someone else.
But you know me.
I'm lazy, so...
I don't know
that side of you at all.
No, stay, stay.
I'll get it.
You like them?
Yeah.
Girls.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Of course I do.
I never hear
about you with girls.
I mean, it's private.
Right, private.
I keep a lot of things private.
Obviously.
I like girls.
Yeah, no shit.
But I also like you.
Lucky me.
Not as person, of course.
Of course not, I'm boring.
But you have a good mouth.
Sorry. Here.
Hello, Father.
Yes, I got your message.
I did answer you, Father.
We spoke yesterday.
Father...
Father, where is Alexei?
My brother Alexei.
Is he there with you?
Are you alone?
Is Polina there?
Polina, she is your wife.
Father, stay calm.
I will call Alexei.
I will call him.
Where the fuck are you?
Dad is alone
and he's freaking out.
I fucking pay you to be there
with him, you asshole!
You still hungry?
No, but thank you.
That was great.
Good.
How is your father?
Ah, you speak Russian now?
I know the word for father.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, Hollander!
You gonna cum for me, Rozanov?
Fucking make me.
Oh!
Oh, fuck, Shane!
Ah!
Ilya...
Ah...
I should...
I should, uh...
I should go.
I should...
Go?
Stay... I can't.
Team meeting in the morning.
I forgot. So...
OK.
You forgot team meeting?
Thank you for the tuna melt.
Hmm.
Um...
Uh...
I'm sorry.
This... I can't.
Hollander.
I just...
I can't, uh...
I can't do this.
Hollander.
I'm sorry.
Are we expecting someone else?
Oh, no, it's just
the three of us. Thank you.
Honey, have you decided
about Wimbledon?
Rolex really wants you there.
I think they're worried their
box is too tennis-y, I think.
Does that mean too white?
I thought you liked
your deal with Rolex.
I do.
Well, you certainly
love the money,
and they're great seats.
I mean, they're
next to a prince,
or, no, actually,
a Swedish princess.
I don't think I
should skip training.
Well, meeting a Swedish
princess could be fun, right?
I don't have time for
that right now, Mom.
-All my time is scheduled.
-I just meant...
I get, like,
two weeks off a year.
I don't want to spend it
next to someone I don't know,
trying to make
conversation about what?
Swedish politics?
OK.
Can I get anyone a drink?
We'll take this Chablis, please.
Three glasses?
Uh, I'll have
a ginger ale, please.
-Oh, we don't have that.
-Sparkling water?
Sure, thank you.
I'm sure you could have a
glass of wine if that's what...
No, I can't.
Not during the season.
Shane...
Yeah?
Is everything all right?
Why? 'Cause I don't want wine?
Well, you just seem tense.
I'm fine.
Well, I think a little trip
to London next summer
for Wimbledon,
just the three of us,
would be fun.
And I think you should
think about it.
We could make a week of it.
Go to a play, see Big Ben.
You loved it
when you were a kid.
You guys should go.
You'd have a great time.
You're the tennis fan, Dad.
They're not gonna send
us the tickets, honey.
It's you they want.
We're just the parents.
You're the main attraction.
Well, then I'll just lie,
tell them I'm coming.
They won't kick you out,
and you can just tell them
I'm sick or something.
-Honey, I... I...
-I don't want you to lie.
That's not who you are.
Sorry. I'm in a weird mood.
It's OK.
Anything you want to talk about?
-Let's, um...
-Let's think about London.
Maybe it could be fun.
I'm just gonna use the washroom.
A Swedish princess?
I don't know.
Hey, man.
Hollander, what the
fuck are you doing right now?
I was about to...
Bullshit! Get your ass
to the Mile End, baby!
My buddy François, the chef,
you remember him?
Oh, yeah?
He's having an after hours
thing at his restaurant.
And get this...
JJ...
The cast of the X Squad movie
they're filming in town is here.
All of them?
-I don't fucking know.
-Get down here!
You remember the restaurant,
right? Le Tambour?
I don't know...
Yes, you bitch!
Good to see you!
OK, guys, this one never
leaves his fucking house.
Tonight is a miracle!
Shane.
Uh, do you have any ginger ale?
I mean, I do, but...
Actually, just a beer, please,
whatever you have on tap.
Shane Hollander can have
whatever he wants.
You keep it then.
It's an honor.
Cool crowd, huh?
You kidding? A bunch of
famous actors are here tonight.
Rose Landry's here, man.
-She is?
-Yeah.
I might be needing
another one of these.
Are you here
to help me finish these fries?
The chef gave them to me,
and they are really good.
I'm not gonna fit
in my costume if I eat them all.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
these are so good!
I'm Rose, by the way.
I'm Shane.
I'm... Wow, I'm a big fan.
Would you be surprised to know
that I'm a fan of yours?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'm a Michigan girl
with three brothers.
Have a fry, Shane Hollander.
Detroit's not gonna
go easy on you tomorrow night.
Uh, I was 8,
and I played this girl who gets
kidnapped and held for ransom.
-Wow.
-By Bill Paxton.
That is terrible.
He was actually
pretty nice to me.
And it was good practice.
Getting kidnapped?
I've been kidnapped
in no less than four movies,
including the one
I'm doing right now.
Fuck! You...
You didn't hear that.
They will literally
have me murdered
if they find out I told you.
My lips are sealed.
OK. Your turn.
Well, I've never been kidnapped.
I mean, there have
been threats, but...
No, not what I meant.
Shane Hollander, 8 years old.
Paint me a picture.
Well, I'm definitely
on the ice somewhere.
The scouting and crazy stuff
didn't start
for another couple years,
so I'm probably just having fun.
Did it stop being fun?
No.
Well, I mean, kind of.
I love it,
but it got more intense,
so I guess I kinda
got more intense too,
if that makes sense.
Yeah, it does.
And I bet that being
the only Asian kid
didn't make it less intense.
I wasn't the only one.
There was one other.
He hated me, though.
Hmm.
I have a Western last name,
so it's like the other kids
kind of forgot
to make fun of me.
And I bet you were pretty
fucking good too, right?
I was all right.
Hmm.
John tapped out at NCAA.
Thank you.
But he still made it to the
frozen four with Princeton.
That's amazing.
He's an agent now, naturally.
Uh, and Peter's in the AHL,
undrafted, but hey.
Still not nothing.
Not nothing indeed.
So, this isn't your first time
in Montreal though, right?
Uh, no.
I was here a few years ago
shooting this
horrible FBI movie.
Under Dark? Kidnapped again?
Come on. No!
-I... I fly a lot.
-I watch a lot of movies.
-That movie is so bad.
-It's not great.
No, it's horrible.
You were really good in it.
-I'm so bad in it.
-No, you're good.
Well, I'm barely in it.
I was here for a week,
and it was the summer.
Mmm. Kind of different
in the winter though, right?
Michigan, remember?
Your winter doesn't scare me.
So, um, are you gonna be in
town a little while this time?
♪♪ Put it on my visa ♪
♪ Don't want you to go, oh ♪
♪ Girl, you my love, oh ♪
♪ Take you inside
to show you I'm real ♪
♪ I'm real ♪
♪ Ploge avem ♪
♪ Baby, I wanna be
dancing with you ♪
♪ Kouche avem ♪
♪ Baby girl, follow me go ♪
♪ I will be
taking you home... ♪♪
Roz, Roz, you gotta see this.
You're gonna shit, man.
-Show him.
-Mm-hmm.
No!
-I know, right?
-She's a huge fucking movie star.
How did he even meet her?
She's shooting in Montreal.
How the fuck do you know that?
It says it right there.
"The two met
at a mutual friend's party,
"according to unnamed sources.
"'I've never seen Rose
this happy, '
the source goes on to say."
I'd be fucking happy if I was
banging Rose Landry.
And there's Rose Landry
wearing a
Shane Hollander jersey.
That's gonna upset
some Detroit fans.
Seems to be getting a reaction
out of the Metro's bench.
No confirmation yet
from Rose Landry's camp,
but the star seems quite happy
to let tongues wag
about her new love,
as long as he doesn't
spoil anything
about the highly anticipated
X Squad sequel.
Movie stars and athletes
seem to have a hard time
resisting each other
these days, don't they?
It's hard to blame either one.
They are definitely
one hot couple.
They are fire!
Hey, I was watching that!
You good, Roz?
Oh, fuck.
I stubbed my toe.
OK, man.
Still jockeying for the top spot
in the Atlantic Division and in
the Eastern Conference at large,
Shane Hollander
and the Montreal Metros
will look to put some
distance tonight
between themselves and their
arch rivals, the Boston Raiders.
But we'll see what Ilya Rozanov
has to say about that.
Yo, come on, let's go!
-We'll get him, buddy.
-Little rust.
In a listless effort,
the visiting Boston Raiders
managed four shots on goal
in the third period.
If you can call 1-0 a victory,
and I guess Montreal will take
what they can get tonight.
But where on the ice
was Shane Hollander?
Where was Ilya Rozanov?
Fuck this shit.
I need to get laid.
Let's go out.
Where?
-We're in Montreal.
-We find a fucking club.
Tell people!
I'm on it.
Jesus fucking Christ.
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
Hi, handsome.
Good game tonight, babe.
No, it wasn't.
No, it wasn't, but you won.
I need a beer.
I bet you do.
Did you watch the game too?
Yeah, I watched a few clips
on Rose's phone,
but it was a sweaty blur.
Miles! Don't be terrible.
I have no problem
watching sweaty blurs.
OK, I want to dance.
-Oh, I don't know.
-I'm beat, man.
Come on! I never get to dance.
OK, that is a lie.
Hey, I want to dance with Shane.
That makes two of us.
-Come on.
-Miles, get us champagne.
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
-Sorry about them.
-Can I have one more please?
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ All the things she said ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ And I'm all mixed up,
feeling cornered and rushed ♪
♪ They say it's my fault
but I want her so much ♪
♪ Want to fly her away
where the sun and rain ♪
♪ Come in over my face,
wash away all the shame ♪
♪ When they stop and stare,
don't worry me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm feeling for her
what she's feeling for me ♪
♪ I can try to pretend
I can try to forget ♪
♪ But it's driving me mad,
going out of my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ All the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
I gotta go to the bathroom.
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ I'm serious shit ♪
♪ I feel totally lost ♪
♪ If I'm asking for help
it's only because ♪
♪ Being with you
has opened my eyes ♪
♪ Could I ever believe
such a perfect surprise? ♪
♪ I keep asking myself ♪
♪ Wondering how
I keep closing my eyes ♪
♪ But I can't block you out ♪
♪ Want to fly to a place
where it's just you and me ♪
♪ Nobody else,
so we can be free ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ Running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said,
all the things she said ♪
♪ Running through my head,
running through my head ♪
♪ All the things she said ♪
♪ This is not enough ♪
♪ I'm in serious shit ♪
♪ I feel totally lost ♪
♪ If I'm asking for help
it's only because ♪
♪ Being with you ♪
♪ Has opened my eyes ♪
♪ Could I ever believe
such a perfect surprise? ♪
♪ I keep asking myself,
wondering how ♪
♪ I keep closing my eyes
but I can't block you out ♪
♪ Want to fly to a place
where it's just you and me ♪♪
MELS